Dreaming is believing.
The Good Night is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Jake Paltrow.
Gary, a musician, is trapped in an unhappy
relationship with his live-in lover, Dora.
He becomes enthralled with a beautiful seductress who enters his dreams, and tries to
control his dream-state so he can spend more and more time with her.
When Gary sees his mystery woman's face on a bus billboard, he discovers
she is real, and fate brings him an opportunity to meet her.
Gary Shaller, played by Martin Freeman.
Dora Epstein, played by Gwyneth Paltrow.
Anna / Melodia, played by Penélope Cruz.
Paul, played by Simon Pegg.
Mel, played by Danny DeVito.
Terry, played by Amber Sealey.
The Good Night is a 2007 fantasy comedy-drama film
written and directed by Jake Paltrow.
The film stars his sister Gwyneth Paltrow, Penélope Cruz, Martin
Freeman, Danny DeVito, Simon Pegg and others.
The movie takes place in London and New York City, where a former pop star (Freeman) who
now writes commercial jingles for a living experiences a mid-life crisis.
The movie was released on the 2007 Sundance Film Festival.
The film explores themes of new york city, dreams,
midlife crisis, obsession, routine.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.